Guide to the Administrative Papers of Chancellor George Bugliarello RG.007
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series II: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Alphabetical Files
    - George Bugliarello Scholarship, 2002 May 31 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - George Bugliarello – 1994 Tribute – Correspondence, 1994 May-August (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Spera Bugliarello (Nee Gefta-Wondrich) – Dissertation – 1924 (copy), Undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - New York Building Congressional Leadership – 1993 Leadership Award (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Dr. Mario Bunge – Correspondence, 1986 August - 2009 January (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Cable – Polytechnic University, 1995 December, 2008 December - 2010 December (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - John D. Calandra Italian American Institute, 2008 December 1 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Campaign for Polytechnic, 1990 August - 1994 November (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Carlo Lotti, 1996 November - 1997 March (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Carlo Messina, 1992 July - 1993 May (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Case for Polytechnic, 1997 October-November (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - "Catalyst for Change" – American Chemical Society's New York Section Symposium, 1993 October (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Center for Advanced Telecommunications Technology (CATT), 1982, 1994, 2004 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Center for Technology and the Cities – Grant Proposal Draft, Undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Andrew Kalotay Associates, 1994 January-June (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Brochures, Undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Cable article, 1995 January (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Ian Domowitz, 1993 December - 1994 March (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Inauguration, 1994 November 16 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – John F. Marshall, 1993 September - 1994 October (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Meetings, 1993 January - 1994 February (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Meeting – Notes, 1994 August 29 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Miscellaneous, 1990 December - 1994 August (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Miscellaneous, 1994 September - 1999 September, Undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Paul Soros, 1995 January (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services – Alfred P. Sloan Foundation - Grant, 1994 April-June (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Alfred P. Sloan Foundation – Hirsch Cohen, 1994 February-October (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Center for Technology & Financial Services - Special Topics in Financial Technology Course, 1995 January-February (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - C.G. Wang – Lithium batteries, 2009 November - 2010 April (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Dato Lee Yee Chang – Correspondence, 2010 October 16 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Chemical Engineering – Sustainable Cities - Course Evaluations, 2005 February (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Chemical Engineering – Biosoma-Environmental Design of the City of the Future (CE 4053), 2008 Fall (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Chemical Engineering - New Student Orientation, 2006 May-July (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Chemical Engineering – Sustainable Cities ( CE 4043), 2003-2004 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Chemical Engineering – Department webpage, 2007 November (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 2009 February - 2010 June (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - China, 2003 November - 2004 April (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Chinese Delegation Roundtable, 2009 January-February (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Chinese Delegation Visit, 2006 September-October (Box 19, Folder 42)
    - The Chronicle, 2002 March, 2003 April-October (Box 19, Folder 43)
    - Chronicle of Higher Education, 2003 April-September (Box 19, Folder 44)
    - Christopher Coccaro – Correspondence, 2009 May-June (Box 19, Folder 45)
    - Cities Transformed – Presentation, Undated (Box 19, Folder 46)
    - City of the Future –Notes, Undated (Box 19, Folder 47)
    - Civil Engineering Department, 1996 April - 2008 October (Box 19, Folder 48)
    - Civilta del Lavoro, Undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
    - Cliff Matthews - Cosmic Beginnings / Religion of Science, 1993-1994 (Box 19, Folder 50)
    - Clifford Goldsmith, 1992 March - 1994 January (Box 19, Folder 51)
    - Coast Guard Academy - Saul Krasmer, 2000 November 14 (Box 19, Folder 52)
    - Columbia Business School speaker series, 1994 March (Box 19, Folder 53)
    - Columbia University, 2000 September-October (Box 19, Folder 54)
    - Comerint: Societa Per Azioni, 1993 April 14 (Box 19, Folder 55)
    - Commencement, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 56)
    - Commencement, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 57)
    - Commencement, 2010 (Box 19, Folder 58)
    - Commission in Higher Education, 1993 April 16 (Box 19, Folder 59)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and University (CICU), 1993 June - 1995 January (Box 19, Folder 60)
    - Commissioner of Buildings, 2005 November 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Committee on Human Rights, 1996 May - 2000 December (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Science Engineering & Public Policy (COSEPP) – American Association for the Advancement of Science, 1988 July-August (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Computer Network: Toward Global Intelligence, 1984 June-December (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Consortium for International Earth Science Information Network (CIESIN), 1993 October 4 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Control of Growth as a Field of Academic Inquiry, 1974 December (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Matteo Convertino, 2010 May-June (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Cooper Union – Al Appleton, 2010 October - 2011 January (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sean Costigan – Lower Manhattan Project, 2010 April -June (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Council for Scientific Society Presidents – "The Future of Science", 1995 December 5 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Council on Foreign Relations – New York Academy of Sciences, 1993 March - 1994 March (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "Creativity: The Hidden Dimension in Engineering and the Challenge to Engineering Education" - – American Society of Engineering Education Conference, 1987 June 21 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - CSEI Catania, 1991 June - 1996 February (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "The Culture of Government Needs to be Less Monolithic", Undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - CUNY, 2004 January-March (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Dias K. Daukeev, 1993 June - 1996 January (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Ruth David – Applied Systems Thinking Prize, 2008 March (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Vincent Del Gatto, 2006 December 6 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Department of Energy – Repot, 1983 August-October (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Donald Othmer – Mayor's Award of Honor for Science & Technology, 1987 February-April (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Department of State and Defense – Landmines – Laurie Freeman, 2010 May (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Dibner Chair, 2007 February 2 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Ian Domowitz – Rapporteur Summary, 1995 March-May (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Dorm Meeting, 1994 February (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Editing Notes, 2011 January (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Education Partnerships, 1989 March (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Educational Commission for Foreign Medical Graduates, 1993 August, 1994 December (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Egypt, 2008 April 18 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Giorgio Einaudi, 2005 March - 2006 February (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Fred Eirich – Obituary, 2005 May 26 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Election 2001– American Association for the Advancement of Science (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Electronic Engineering Times, 1991 January (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Elwin S. Larsen Tribute, 1991 April (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Emergency Management for Higher Education, 2008 October-December (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - "Engineering and the Future" - Correspondence, 1994 May 23 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - Engineering College of Aarhus, Denmark, 2004 June 30 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - Engineering Education for the 21th Century, 1987 October 10 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Engineering News-Record, 1984 November, 1992 December - 1993 February (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - Engineers Forum on Sustainability, 2004 January-March (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - Environmental Management Association, 2009 March (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - Annual International Conference on Ethical Issues in Biomedical Engineering, 2009 April (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - Evangelos Limpantoudis - RESTRICT, 2010 May 13 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - Guiseppe Ferro, 2009 June 5 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - Florida A&M University – Industry Day 2007 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - Efi Fourfoula-Georgiou – University of Minnesota, 2008 February - 2009 January (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - Future of Engineering – Notes, 1996 March 23 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - De Gao – Outstanding Graduate Award – RESTRICT, 2010 March (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - Mannela Garcia, 1993 November 5 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - Germany's New States, 1993 May (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Gift Acknowledgements, 1992 March-June, 1994 January-April (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Tony B. Giordano, 1992 August - 1995 October (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - William T. Golden, 2007 January (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Harvey Goldstein – Harvest International, 1992 October, 1994 February (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Thomas Graedel, 2005 February-April (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - Monty Graham, 2010 May (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Richard Grasso, 1993 December (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Green Grants – Richard Wener, 2009 June (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - Seymour S. Greenfield, 1992 December 10 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - Greenwald Foundation, 1989 January, 2000 June (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - Guest Lecture – U.S. Coast Guard Academy, 2000 November 14 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - Richard E. Hanley, Journal of Urban Technology, 1994 April 29 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Morag Hann - Urban Initiative, 2006 October 17 (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - Garth R. Harding - "Will Megacities Survive", 2010 June (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Hemorheology & Bioengineering, Undated (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - Herman F. Mark Memorial Service, 1992 April 13 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Holiday Card List, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 66)
    - Honorary Degrees, 2009 December (Box 20, Folder 67)
    - Honorary Degrees – Criteria for Candidates, 1980 November 19 (Box 20, Folder 68)
    - Humanity 3000 Symposium No. 1 Proceedings, 2000 August 12-16 (Box 20, Folder 69)
    - Tin-Kan Hung, 2007 October - 2009 July (Box 20, Folder 70)
    - Hyper Intelligence, 1984, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 71)
    - IASP World Conference on Science and Technology Parks, 1997 March-June (Box 20, Folder 72)
    - The Ideal of Civil Engineering", 1993 January 25 (Box 20, Folder 73)
    - Ernesto Illy, 1993 October-December (Box 20, Folder 74)
    - Indiana University – Michael Conneally, 2008 March 18 (Box 20, Folder 75)
    - Industrial Technology Research Institute, 1993 October (Box 20, Folder 76)
    - Infrastructure Technology & Finance, 1995 April 7 (Box 20, Folder 77)
    - Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers – Industry Relations Luncheon, 1990 December, 1991 February (Box 20, Folder 78)
    - Institute for Science, Engineering and Public Policy - Resident Scholar, 1998 May-December (Box 20, Folder 79)
    - Integrated Research for Civil Infrastructure, 1997 February (Box 20, Folder 80)
    - International Education for Technology Management, 1992 February 20 (Box 20, Folder 81)
    - International Higher Education Academy of Sciences, 1993 December - 1994 May (Box 20, Folder 82)
    - International Higher Education Academy of Sciences, 1997 March - 2005 June (Box 20, Folder 83)
    - Italian American Advisory Council, 1994 April 25 (Box 20, Folder 84)
    - Italian International Technology Fund, 1991 March 25 (Box 20, Folder 85)
    - Italian Scientists and Scholars of North America Foundation, 2006 December - 2008 Novemeber (Box 20, Folder 86)
    - Dr. Linda K. Jacobs, 1994 March-October (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Japan-American Frontiers of Engineering Symposium, 2010 July (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Journal of Medical Implants and Devices, 2009 June 26 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Journal of Russian Technology, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Journal of Urban Technology, 2007 January - 2009 March (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Dr. Ilan Juran – Urban Infrastructure / Sustainability Courses, 2004 September - 2007 January (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Ken Keller – Johns Hopkins School of Advanced International Studies, Bologna Center, 2006 May - 2007 January (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Robert Kelley – Media Planet, 2009 November 13 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Melissa Knothe Tate, 2010 May 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Korean Academy of Science & Technology, 2004 March-May, 2006 April-December (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Dr. Erich Kunhardt, 2006 August 9 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Frank Lahainer-Laniezi, 1993 December 20 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Giovanni Latorre, 2002 September (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Lawrence Livermore National Laboratory, 2003 March - 2006 November (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Leadership Seminar Series, 1996 February-October (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Don Lebell, 2008 October - 2009 March (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Dato Lee Yee Cheong, 2010 February 5 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Liikeenjohdon Instituutti Foretagsledningsinstitutet – Finnish Institute of Management, 1992 May 18 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Local Initiatives Support Corporation – Bodega Project, 2005 September, 2006 March (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Long Island, 1993 January 27 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Long Island Lightning Company, 1994 April 13 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Long Island & Westchester Advisory Board, 1994 January (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - MacArthur Foundation, 1994 November 4 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Magazine - La Citta E La Scienza, "Un Politecnico Dal Nulla", 1999 October 24 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Gordon Mahon – Recommendation - RESTRICT, 1993 June-September (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - 2010 Marconi Prize, 2010 June (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Marconi Society, 1981-1989 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Marconi Society, 1992-1997 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Marconi Society, 2001-2006 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Marconi Society, 2007 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Marconi Society, 2008 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Marconi Society, 2009 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Marconi Society, Undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Master in Security Studies, 2002 August 26 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Master in Urban Sustainability – Notes, Undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Master of Science in Management, 1988 February 25 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Master of Technology, 1991 November (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - "Mastermind of Metrotech" – Brooklyn Progress, 1990 September (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Mayor's Advisory Council on Development & Recycling Markets, 1992 December - 1993 June (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1994 April-December (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1995, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 1998 July (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology – RESTRICT, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Mayor's Award of Honor for Excellence in Science and Technology - Nomination – Eli M. Pearce - RESTRICT, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Mayor's Award for Excellence in Science and Technology, 2000 August - 2001 February (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Mayor's Commission for Science & Technology, 1989 March 15 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Arthur W. Mellon Foundation – Proposal, 1981 May (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Mentoring, 2007 September-December (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Metrocities, 2005 November - 2006 May (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Mexico City – Urban Sustainability, 2008 October 2 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Henry Q. Middendorf, 1993 March 16 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - "The Middle East in 1990", William B. Quandt, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Middle States Association, 1993 February-July (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Joel Miele – Commissioner, Department of Buildings - Silk Road Project, 1994 May 9 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Mildred Topp Othmer – Memorial, 1998 July-October (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous, 1974-1993 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Miscellaneous, 1993 March - 1996 February (Box 21, Folder 57)
    - Miscellaneous, 2004 February-March (Box 21, Folder 58)
    - Miscellaneous, 2006 December - 2010 October (Box 21, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous – Correspondence, 2009 April (Box 21, Folder 60)
    - Miscellaneous - Mailings, 2008 June-September (Box 21, Folder 61)
    - Miscellaneous – Old Publications, 1958-1959, Undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous - Original Presentation Drawings, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous – Papers & Drafts, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous – Press, 1994 January-June, 1996 October (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - David Mitchell, 1991 December 13 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - William C.W. Mow, 1994 February-March (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Sophje Nalecz, 2009 September (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Nanjing International Center for Urban Innovation, 2008 August-September (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - National Consortium for Specialized Secondary Schools, 1994 May 16 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - National Medal of Technology – Nomination Evaluation Committee, 1991 February 19 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Science Foundation, 1992 October-November (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - National Science Foundation – Bodegas Project Proposal, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - National Science Foundation - Bugliarello Visit, 2006 January (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - National Science Foundation – Modeling of Mobile Customer Service Interaction Systems, 2002 January 7 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - National Science Foundation - Proposal Review Criteria, 2006 April-May (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - National Science Foundation – Workshop on Engineering the Service Sector, July 23-24, 2001, 2001 June-August (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - NATO – Dr. Anthony R. Tomazinis, 1999 January-February (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - NATO – Italy, 1993 March-June (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - NATO – Robert Rines, 1993 September - 1994 July (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - NATO - Turkey - 1993 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - NATO - Turkey, 1994 January-March (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - NATO - Turkey, 1994 April-May (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - NATO - Turkey, 1994 June-September (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - NATO - Turkey, 1995-1996, Undated (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - NATO - Uzbekistan, 1997 January-September, Undated (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - NATO – Uzbekistan – Visa, 1996 April-November (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - NEC Foundation of America, 1992 April 13 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Paolo Nespoli, 2007 October-November (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Nova Publishers, 2007 January-April (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1994 July - 1999 March (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - New York Academy of Sciences, 1998 October - 2000 May (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - New York Academy of Sciences - Committee on Human Rights of Scientists, 1996 October 16 - 2001 May (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - New York Academy of Sciences - New York City Mayor's Award in Technology, 1997 December - 1998 December (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - New York City Partnership, 1990-1992 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - New York State - Office of Management & Budget, 1993 March 5 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Ohio Aerospace Institute, 1998 October 6 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Optimization of Interaction of Infrastructure System Designs, 2007 September-October (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Oregon –"Biology, Machines and Society" Lecture, 1999 January (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development, 1994 October (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Simon Ostrach – Distinguished Lecture Series – September 16, 2008, 2007 December - 2008 October (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Janka Ovcharovichova, 2010 April (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Pace University – Honorary Degree, 1994 May 28 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Eliana Papadakis, 2009 July 29 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Parise Yorke - Technology in Merchandising, 1999 April - 2001 March (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Parliament of the World's Religions, 1993 April-May (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - Pergamon Press - Michael Boswood, 1992 January (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - Personal - Schillinger Family, 2011 January 20 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - Henry Petrosky – Duke University, 1995 April - 2006 May (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - Physics Department, 1991 December - 1994 August (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - Plenary Talk Workshop on Earth Systems Engineering - University of Colorado, 2001 October 5 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - Politecnico Di Milano, 2002 February 12 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - Robin Pollack - Windstorm Mitigation Program, 2010 February 12 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - Marco Polo Society, 2002 December, 2007 December (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - Polytechnic University - Leadership Team, 2008 October-November (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic - Long-Term Goals, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Polytechnic – Miscellaneous, 1991, 2003, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Polytechnic – Name Change, 1986 January 9 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Polytechnic - Overview, 1993 April, August (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Polytechnic - Retired Professors Group, 2010 April (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Polytechnic - Sesquicentennial Convocation Meeting, 2005 May (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Polytechnic - Statistics & Reports, 1975, 1993-1994, 2007 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Polytechnic - Strategic Planning, 1991 November - 1992 February (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Polytechnic - Strategic Planning, 1992 March-August, 1993 October (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Polytechnic - Strategic Planning, 1996, 1998, Undated (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Polytechnic Corporation – Board Meeting, 1991-1995 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Polytechnic Reporter Interview, 2006 September 13 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Power Point Presentations - Table of Contents, Undated (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - President's Files List, Undated (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Dr. Robert A. Pritzker, 2003 October (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Promise Fund, 1991 February - 1994 April (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Raffaele Cisternino, 2003 April –August, 2007 September (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Red Cross, 1993 December (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Regional Plan Association, 1993-1996 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Honorary Degree, 2004 March-September (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Research Proposal on Studies of Blood Flow in and Adjacent to Blood Pumps, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - "Rethinking America's industry," By George Bugliarello, 1992 June 4 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Richard Wener – "Design of Cities" class, 2007 March 1 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "The Role of University, Industry and International Collaboration" – Seminar on Changing Characteristics of Science and Technology in International Development – National Research Council, 1993 September 27 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Otto Romanelli, 2001 May 18 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Rome – New York Sister City Program, 1993 April - 1995 May (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Dr. Rustum Roy, 2005 August - 2007 January (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Subrata Saha – Ethics Debate, 2010 April (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Subrata Saha – Ethics Conference, 2006 February - 2007 April (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - George Schillinger, 1992 December - 2010 July, Undated (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - Dr. William Schockley – Sigma Xi Convocation Cancellation - 1, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Dr. William Schockley – Sigma Xi Convocation Cancellation - 2, 1968 (Box 23, Folder 33)